<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fuzzylogiq&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on fuzzylogiq&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>macad.uk Talk 2018</title>
      <link>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/post/macaduk-talk-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/post/macaduk-talk-2018/</guid>
      <description>Slides from my talk at macad.uk A couple of days ago I gave a talk to the Mac Admin and Developer Conference in London on the past, present and (not terribly long) future of macOS Server, and how you might plan to move away from it.
The slides are up on my github talks repo at https://github.com/fuzzylogiq/talks/blob/master/MACADUK-20180220/The_Sky_Is_Falling.pdf
Be warned, they&amp;rsquo;re 42MB!
It was a great conference, as any meeting of our brilliant community tends to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Amoeba InstantOn Driver Installs</title>
      <link>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/post/rogue-amoeba-echelon-installs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 14:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/post/rogue-amoeba-echelon-installs/</guid>
      <description>We recently had a request from a user to package the Piezo app so they could easily record Skype conversations and other computer audio. The user had been running the app from their home folder but then needed admin creds in order to install InstantOn - which is Rogue Amoeba&amp;rsquo;s audio driver that can instantly start recording audio from apps without restarting them. The app shows the dialog to install the driver under Install Extras&amp;hellip; in the Piezo menu, and also if the user tries to record from an app whose audio stream it can&amp;rsquo;t immediately connect to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problems with disabling the sync of Desktop and Documents to iCloud</title>
      <link>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/post/icloud-desktop-and-documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 16:17:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fuzzylogiq.github.io/post/icloud-desktop-and-documents/</guid>
      <description>In 10.12 Apple introduced the ability for users to sync their Documents and Desktop folder with iCloud so that they would be the same on any computer they were using. In 10.12.4 they gave us the ability to disable it (Rich Trouton has a very informative blog post on how to do so here.) You might think that setting the preference (allowCloudDesktopAndDocuments=false in com.apple.applicationaccess) means you&amp;rsquo;d be safe from users hiving off all their local data from those folders to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>